# Gonzalo Cibeira

♥ Valencia, Spain ■ cibeiragonzalo@gmail.com 🛘 603394606 🛅 in/gonzalocibeira

#### SUMMARY

An independent, curious and self-motivated Marketing graduate with 5+ years of experience on various business roles, ranging from churn to sales analysis, strategic planning and CSM. I'm always looking for a challenge and new thing to learn!

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Manager, Customer Success

Cubyn

January 2022 - July 2022, Remote (Spain/France)

- Be the single point of contact between Cubyn and it's customers.
- · Onboard and advise custromer's on how to grow their business with teh help of our products.
- · Help developing new features to solve customer's pain points and unlocking new deals.
- Highlights: Managed a 40M € GMV customer portfolio Managed the entire rehaul of the Cubyn Help Center Successfully onboarded several +3M € customers.

## Sr. Strategic Planner

Telecom Argentina S.A.

June 2020 - January 2022, Buenos Aires

- · Create and challenge CapEx budget for the home internet and TV verticals.
- · Communicate area goals and achievements to company stakeholders & C-level executives.
- · Assure that the business roadmap & targets are achieved.
- · Help develop sales & retention policies.
- Highlights: Created a smooth communication loop with all stakeholders Successfully implemented regular progress reviews with C-level execs.

# Ssr. Business Intelligence Analyst - B2C

Telecom Argentina S.A.

December 2018 - May 2020, Buenos Aires

- · Create & maintain the sector's BI stack.
- · Build ad hoc reports.
- · Provide insights & advice to help improve the sales figures.
- · Analyze impact of new sales policies.
- · Highlights: Modernized the team's BI stack Generated insights that led to a 5% increase in sales.

### **Churn Prevention Analyst**

Telecom Argentina S.A.

February 2018 - November 2018, Buenos Aires

- · Understand and analyze main churning reasons.
- · Implement strategies to reduce churn in the company & analyze their impact.
- · Create and monitor KPIs.
- · Present the area results.
- · Highlights: Found and corrected several metric deviations Successfully implemented churn reducing strategies (-7% on some client clusters).

#### **Churn Prevention Analyst**

Cablevision Argentina S.A.

January 2017 - January 2018, Buenos Aires

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelors Degree in Marketing**

UADE (Universidad Argentina de la Empresa) · Buenos Aires · 2019

## **COURSEWORK**

#### **Full Stack Dev**

Coderhouse · 2022 · CSS, HTML, SASS, JavaScript

#### **SKILLS**

Budgeting, Account management, BI tools, CRM, CSM, Marketing, Jira, Planning, Strategic thinking, HTML, CSS, SASS, GIT, Javascript, SQL, Agile

Spanish (native), English (fluent)